nikkisfreebiejeebies.com 2012-12-11

# Nikki's Freebie Jeebies : Privacy Policy

NikkisFreebieJeebies is committed to user privacy. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

We can be reached via e-mail at [nikki@nikkisfreebiejeebies.com](mailto:nikki@nikkisfreebiejeebies.com)

This policy covers NikkisFreebieJeebies.com, Please be advised that our advertisers all have their own, possibly different, policies. Should you click through one of our links and travel to one of our advertisers, we encourage you to read the privacy policies provided on the advertisers sites, and those of all web sites you visit.

Below is a summary of NikkisFreebieJeebies.com's online privacy policy.

Types and uses of personal information.

The only information this website collects from you is your email address and only if you sign up to receive our newsletter. This information is only used to send out our daily newsletter(s). This information is never shared or sold.

Linked web sites

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

Cookies

NikkisFreebieJeebies does not use cookies.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies

This site contains links to other sites. Freebie Jeebies is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [nikki@nikkisfreebiejeebies.com](mailto:nikki@nikkisfreebiejeebies.com)

Nikki Russell  
c/o NikkisFreebieJeebies P.O. Box 9738 Wilmington, DE 19809
